// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which fruit is known for having the highest vitamin C content?",
    answer: "Kiwi",
    options: ["Apple", "Kiwi", "Strawberry", "Orange"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the world's most popular fruit based on consumption?",
    answer: "Tomato",
    options: ["Banana", "Apple", "Mango", "Tomato"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which fruit is also known as the 'king of fruits'?",
    answer: "Durian",
    options: ["Durian", "Mangosteen", "Pineapple", "Watermelon"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What fruit is used to make traditional guacamole?",
    answer: "Avocado",
    options: ["Tomato", "Mango", "Avocado", "Papaya"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Which fruit is known for its ability to ripen other fruits due to the release of ethylene gas?",
    answer: "Banana",
    options: ["Banana", "Apple", "Cherry", "Grape"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following fruits is a good source of potassium?",
    answer: "Banana",
    options: ["Grape", "Orange", "Blueberry", "Banana"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Which fruit has varieties known as 'Honeycrisp' and 'Granny Smith'?",
    answer: "Apple",
    options: ["Pear", "Apple", "Plum", "Cherry"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "Which fruit is known as a 'superfood' for its high antioxidant content?",
    answer: "Blueberry",
    options: ["Apple", "Blueberry", "Orange", "Grape"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "What fruit is typically used to make the Italian dessert tiramisu?",
    answer: "None",
    options: ["Raspberry", "Cherry", "Pear", "None"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "Which fruit is known to contain the enzyme bromelain, which can break down proteins?",
    answer: "Pineapple",
    options: ["Papaya", "Pineapple", "Kiwi", "Starfruit"],
  },
];
